{
    "id": "90941979ac0c4c91bc786d9cf5989543",
    "title": "So And Such Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was ....................... a hot day.",
            "description": "We use 'such' before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "08203aa1ee47404c9b64e00abc63c04e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ....................... kind.",
            "description": "We use 'so' before an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e29f01768ecb42f089e2380dd6301c2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ...................... a lot of problems that I am losing hope.",
            "description": "Such is used before adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2d16869c2d04587af53ae2d24ccf8dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Never have I seen ........................ beautiful woman.",
            "description": "We use 'such a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "so a",
                "so",
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2bf25e96cb8041a08fa310988cfe60ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never seen ........................... food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so much",
                "so many",
                "such much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df15fa2c690843e5930d61d66847bb17"
        },
        {
            "question": "Never have I seen .............................. dirty kitchen.",
            "description": "We use 'such a/an' before adjective + singular countable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so",
                "so a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c7db41491c14224a1b84f90b28e53cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never seen ........................... a good person.",
            "description": "Such is used before (adjective) + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "so much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0ae3a613ea3498aa037cfbd729052be"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are ........................... idiots.",
            "description": "We use such before a noun with or without an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such an",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b3de9ef5034747ffa53d889810c75c57"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has got ...................... strange manners.",
            "description": "Such is used before a noun with or without an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aea1275babd44263aabdd7e959d198de"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ..................... patient with his students.",
            "description": "We use 'so' before adjectives and adverbs. ",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b5ecac7af0f4ac88a278b5e212c1f0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you talk ........................ loudly?",
            "description": "We can use so before adverbs.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bd10c3216d24be68d1892cdaefd1f75"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got ............................. much to do, and ................. little time.",
            "description": "We can use 'so' before much, many, few and little. ",
            "answers": [
                "so, so",
                "so, such",
                "such, so",
                "such, such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4959a5a5ec84962baf76a5078ea8707"
        }
    ]
}